thepirateschest.net 2012-10-27

# Download Movies, Software, Games, Music and More - TPC - Privacy Policy

ThePiratesChest (see [ "TOS" ](http://www.thepirateschest.net/tos.php) ) considers that respect of privacy on the Internet is of utmost importance. This statement presents the rules applied by ThePiratesChest for the collection and dissemination of personal information given by users on the site. They apply to all "ThePiratesChest Sites", i.e. all sites within the "ThePiratesChest.net” domain. 

What information is collected by ThePiratesChest?   
Standard use of the Site   
In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. The only information we gather during a general navigation on the Site is the information intended for the server logs: IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system and information such as the site from which you are connected, pages visited, and the dates and times of those visits. 

Collect of Personal Information   
If you subscribe to a newsletter, log on to certain ThePiratesChest sites, request information, send any comments or if you join a discussion group or electronic mailing list, you will need to provide some personal information : name and e-mail address, for example. Such information is collected only with your permission and is stored in different databases and mailing lists belonging to ThePiratesChest. If you make a purchase over the Internet, you may be asked to provide your credit card information. These data are transferred to a secure payment online, hosted outside ThePiratesChest. ThePiratesChest does not keep credit card information.   
The registration of personal information leads to the submission of a cookie* on certain sites of ThePiratesChest. By setting this cookie, ThePiratesChest will remember your personal details at the next visit so you do not have to re-enter the same information. This helps us to improve the quality of services that we offer.   
Participation in electronic discussion groups means that other participants in the group that you have chosen (including those who are not Site Administrators) will be aware of any personal information that you choose to disclose. In some open discussion groups the information is public. 

What does ThePiratesChest do with the information it collects?   
Standard use of the Site   
The information collected during the navigation in the "ThePiratesChest.net" area is used to analyze trends and the use of the site in order to improve its usefulness. No personal information is attached there. 

Personal Information   
ThePiratesChest may use such information to:   
* Contact you - either in response to a request or a suggestion, or to send you news, documents, publications, and so on;   
* Confirm your entries on the site;   
* "Remember" your online profile and preferences;   
* Statistical analysis performing. 

What will happen if I do not want to provide personal information?   
Providing personal information on the Site is optional. If you do not want to deliver information of this kind, you can always surf the Site, but you will not be able to access the entire Service and its Information. 

Removal or modification of information   
You can delete or modify your personal information at any time by returning to the page where you registered them or by contacting the coordinator of the page. If the page in question does not provide any information on this subject, you can contact Support(at)thepirateschest(dot)net for more information.   
If you are not the issuer of personal information that concerns you and want to have it removed, you can send your request to Support(at)thepirateschest(dot)net 

Security   
The personal data entrusted to the Site will not be sold or transferred to any third party. Any information provided to ThePiratesChest by users of the Site is preserved with the utmost care and maximum safety. It will be used only in the manner described in this privacy policy, or according to the special rules of visited sites or in a manner to which you have explicitly consented. ThePiratesChest uses techniques and a variety of measures to ensure the safety of information stored in its systems and protects them from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.   
All our volunteers (see "Moderators" - TOS) who have access to personal information or are associated with the processing of these data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of every user of the Site, which covers the personal information.   
The Site provides links to sites outside the "ThePiratesChest.net" area and could not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content located on them. 

Modifications   
Any modification of these terms can be made at any time without prior publication or announcement. 

Contact   
For any questions or inquiries about our privacy policy, you can contact us at Support(at)thepirateschest(dot)net 

*Cookie A cookie is a small file that a Web server sends to your browser. It is normally used to assign your computer a unique identification and securely store information: identity of the user, passwords, preferences, online profiles. It is stored on the hard drive of your computer. You can refuse to have cookies delivered by ThePiratesChest sites by changing the settings of your browser. Cookies installed in your computer can come from many Internet sites. To protect the confidentiality of data, your browser allows Web sites to access cookies they themselves have sent, not to those that others have sent.
